  admin-merge-fix                       79c678d feat(admin): add expert pending approval flow
  dev                                   c51fde2 feat: Implement comprehensive event management, an admin panel with user and audit log features, and email template management across frontend and backend.
  feature/ai                            193cf5f [behind 1] feat(admin): add pending approvals to admin dashboard stats
  feature/frontend/admin                79c678d feat(admin): add expert pending approval flow
  feature/frontend/dashboard-mvp        f4473b2 feat: save current dashboard as pro view
  feature/frontend/dashboard-pro        f4473b2 feat: save current dashboard as pro view
  feature/frontend/event-enhancements   79c678d [ahead 6, behind 2] feat(admin): add expert pending approval flow
  feature/frontend/profile-enhancements c51fde2 feat: Implement comprehensive event management, an admin panel with user and audit log features, and email template management across frontend and backend.
* feature/seeder                        a3cf3bb [ahead 13, behind 2] feat: add admin routes for audit logs, user role approval/rejection, and email template management.
+ refactor/core-workflow                c51fde2 feat: Implement comprehensive event management, an admin panel with user and audit log features, and email template management across frontend and backend.
  refactor/user-flow                    a3cf3bb feat: add admin routes for audit logs, user role approval/rejection, and email template management.
  test/restore-stash                    caa2a74 feat(frontend): restore dashboard and onboarding updates; admin moderation enhancements
  trial/9062444                         9062444 Enhance event details: remove redundant price info, add venue, refine UI, add people tab table view, fix build errors
  trial/ebcd0a8                         ebcd0a8 feat(ai): add proposal generator endpoint using provider abstraction; groq/ollama support with TESTING stub; add schemas and unit test
